BOND'S STRATEGY TO STAY ALIVE
Peak laziness.
Miss Anya,
you'll get in trouble with your teacher
if you don't do your homework.
Okee.
Bond's Special Power
Precognition
Hide-and-seek time with Anya!
Borf!
Eek! The power went out!
I have a surprise for you, Bond!
Right this way.
Guy from the Research Lab
I'm finally found you, Number 8!
Now you'll have to die!
Borf!
Bond!
You mustn't cry. He lived
a happy life in the end.
What? You want to say goodbye?
Borf.
Anya is busy with homework.
I don't have time to play.
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry, Bond. We were out of
dog food, but I forgot to buy more.
I think Loid is going to be
home late tonight, too.
I'll try to make your dinner with
what we have around the house.
Borf.
Okay, I'll do my best!
Bond! Your dinner's ready!
Borf.
Bond!
Cause of Death
Loid was kind enough to make a list of all the
things dogs can't eat, so it should be simple!
Your dinner's ready!
Resolution!!
If you make Mama angry,
she'll kill you, so be careful.
Bond!
Well, he just wouldn't
eat the dinner I made.
It's over
Come now, Bond. You mustn't get all riled up.
Oh, no. Are you sick?
is gone
will make dinner
Death
comes home early
will make dinner
Survival
Work
Oh, it's you, Bond! What's the matter?
Ah, thanks for finishing it off.
Now I can go home early.
Bond!
Doggie!
Thanks!
Where'd this stray come from? Shoo, shoo!
How dare you get food
elsewhere?! You bad boy!
A dog!
Draw eyebrows on him!
My mission tonight is to obtain
a sample of the truth serum
being developed by
Born Industries, Gerrulimus.
As usual, this was a tall order, so I didn't
have time to gather any information.
Go, right now.
I won't be able to infiltrate
the premises with a disguise.
I'll just have to force my way in.
Borf!
What?! Bond?! What's he doing here?!
Quiet down! The enemy will find us!
Wait, is it just you?
Where are Yor and Anya? Did you
get away from them during a walk?
I don't know what's going
on here, but go home!
I'm working right now!
Borf!
Borf, borf, borf!
What? You want to play?
I'm busy right now. It'll have to wait.
Borf! Borf!
Hey, come back here!
The enemy base is that way!
He's leading me down a
route that's deserted?
I don't remember training him to do that...
Did he learn that prior?
Come to think of it, there were rumors that
Born Industries was involved in Project Apple.
Did you come here because you knew that?
Are you trying to do this for your... no.
Are you trying to get revenge for your
friends who were experimented on?
You...
B... Borf!
All right. Let's get through
our missions together!
Since I lack information,
relying on your nose is my best option!
Borf!
So this must be the lab.
There are safes everywhere.
Which one has Gerrulimus?
Their security's tight, so it'll be tough
to go through each one separately.
Who knows when I'll get home?
Why'd we get called back here?
Apparently, they found a defect.
Shit! They're back.
I'll keep the enemy busy.
You head back home!
This is going to be a long battle.
Bo-borf!
Where in the world were you?
Now eat your dinner!
Borf! Borf!
Hm? Don't worry. Most of the staff
has clocked out for the day.
Hey.
Wait...
Damn that chief. Why'd we
get called back here?
Apparently, they found a defect.
Our delivery date moved up,
too. Give us a break.
Stop complaining. We're getting
pressured from high up, and...
The door's unlocked...
Hey, what the hell is this?!
"T. Bandit"?
Who's that?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
What the hell? It's right here.
Damn it. Who pulled this prank—
Hey, thanks... for opening that up!
Wh-Who the hell are you guys?! S-Someone—
Not bad. Thanks to you,
I completed my mission smoothly.
Now I can go home earlier than I thought.
Is it good?
Borf!
Goodness, you had me so worried.
I looked for you everywhere.
I see. You're that happy that you were
able to get back at Born Industries?
Good for you.
All right. Let's stop by the supermarket on
our way home so I can cook you a special meal.
Borf! Borf!
DAMIAN'S FIELD RESEARCH TRIP
Lord Damian, if you don't hurry and
wake up, you'll be late to roll call.
As punishment for being late to roll call,
you are to help the Dorm Mother.
Until then, you are prohibited
from leaving the dormitory.
This is quite rare for you.
Though it is not a school day,
it is not elegant to live a
slovenly lifestyle, Mr. Desmond.
I'll be more careful, sir.
Lord Damian, were you up late studying again?
I need to hurry up and earn more Stellas.
You're working way too hard.
Oh, also! I hear our teacher is going
to take us to the movies today.
We might get to see the new
20,000 Steps under the Sea!
And on our way back, we're going
to have roast beef at Wimpsons!
Let's finish up so we can
meet up with everyone!
Yay, roast beef!
I'm not going.
I'm going to be studying in my room.
What? But it's our day off today.
I said I'm not going.
I'm not changing my mind.
But...
Sir, can we go see whatever movie we want?
I want to see 20,000 Steps under the Sea.
Well, we'll see...
Come on, please? We should definitely
see 20,000 Steps under the Sea.
I'm not like them.
While they're busy playing, I'm going
to work hard to get to the top.
Damian, continue working hard
so as not to shame the Desmond name.
So Father will praise me again.
You two!
Go over there.
This is Damian's penalty.
Improper dress and eating
outside of designated hours.
As punishment, go help the Dorm Mother.
Thank you very much!
Wha—
What are you two doing here? Why didn't
you go out with the rest of them?
This is our punishment.
Let's get this over with already.
I said that I'm not going to play.
Stop being so stubborn, Lord Damian!
You nerd!
Whatever. You don't need to hang out with me.
You two go on and have fun.
I mean, if you really think about it,
those other guys lack any taste if they're
going to a movie on a beautiful day like this.
Exactly. What's really in
right now is doing laundry.
Not to mention, look!
We can even pretend to be Imperial Scholars!
If you want your Stellas, come and get me!
Hey! That cape belongs to me, you jerk!
Come back here and work, you three.
Elegant...
Your friendship... preciously elegant.
You look like you want to go on a picnic, lad.
I do not!
Hm.
Talking and messing around while
you're supposed to be working...
I have a new punishment for you three.
What?!
Go on the field research trip
with Mr. Green, our custos.
Aren't picnics fun?!
I'm gonna die!
You can go down the river
while being on the premises!
Isn't Eden grand?
We're going to die!
I'm gonna die!
Don't you worry. I used to be in the navy!
Just relax and have fun!
All right! Let's keep going
until we hit the lake upstream!
It's a great spot!
Moderate exercise is good for the brain, too!
Just sitting at your desk isn't necessarily
the most effective way to study!
Well, this exercise isn't moderate!
Come on, lads! You're going to have
to row to the left as hard as you can,
or we're going to crash into that rock!
Sir! There's a waterfall
right in front of us!
Lord Damian!
Save me!
I'm the second son of the
prestigious Desmond family!
We're coming right now!
Hey, lads.
I'm the heir to the Elman family!
I'm the successor to the Egeburg fam—
L-Lord Damian, you need to survive,
even if no one else can!
Yes! Make your dreams come
true for our sakes, as well!
You two...
Please hurry to the boat! Before
the last of our strength fails us!
Damn it!
I can see you're having fun out there,
but you can stand up.
And the current isn't fast at all.
Huh?
It was only fast because I was paddling.
Come on. You need to get some firewood
so we can start a fire before you catch cold.
Yes, sir!
It's so warm...
Now that I've calmed down, I'm kinda hungry.
Since you're wet already,
why don't we catch fish in the river?
What? We don't have sandwiches
or anything prepared?
We don't have anything fancy like that.
You're Eden students!
We'll get what we need right here!
Huh? But...
I'll get you some string and nets.
You figure out the best way to use them!
What?
It's so good!
Indeed!
Ain't it, though?
The roast beef at Wimpsons ain't half bad,
but nothing beats prey
you've caught yourself.
It's good! It's so good!
Yum!
Why am I having fun right now?
While I'm messing around here,
others are studying...
Doesn't the gentle breeze feel nice, lad?
The sound of the fire popping
as the flames dance...
The rustling of the trees and
the smell of the dirt...
Relaxing and letting your five senses
take control ain't half bad, is it?
I won't become an Imperial Scholar
just by spacing out here.
Oh? Did you know that the most
recent studies in neuroscience
suggest that your brain feels really
revitalized when you're spacing out?
Apparently, it affects your
memory and imagination.
So famous creators and athletes make sure
to give themselves time to space out.
While you're spacing out, you might be able
to get all eight Stellas before you know it.
No way!
Space out...
Space out, space out, space out...
Lord Damian, I don't think
that's really spacing out...
He might be more simple-minded than I thought.
All right.
Your clothes have mostly dried,
so let's walk toward the lake.
Apparently, the students call
this lake "Stella Lake."
Stella! Let's go!
Lord Damian, you're way
too obsessed with Stellas.
Pic-pic-pic-pic-picnic!
Oh, yeah. Lately, people in the south
have been using the code word "picnic"
for defecting to the West
through a third country.
Sir, are you trying to sell us to the West?!
You can't defect just by walking
a couple of kilometers.
I wonder why they go to the West.
I wonder if snacks just
taste better in the West.
Who knows?
Just look at how beautiful
the night sky is in Ostania.
There's nothing to worry about!
Once Lord Damian becomes an adult,
he'll make Ostania even better!
Yeah!
Hey...
Oh? Do you wish to be a politician
in the future? That's admirable!
Well, my father is one, so...
I see, yes. It's wonderful to be
able to work hard toward a goal.
By the way, my dream is to
become a cosmonaut!
Is it? Well, that's cool!
I, I...
don't really have one!
Oh, you don't, eh?
Well, that's perfectly fine.
Actually, I want to live my
life eating lots of snacks!
Splendid! Now, what kind of dream is that?
You'll have to think earnestly about
how to make that possible.
How are you going to stay healthy
even if you're eating a lot of snacks?
What? That sounds like a pain.
And we're here.
Wow! The stars are reflecting on the
water! It looks like the universe!
Look, lads. It's almost as if
you can grab the stars.
Lame.
Do you think we wasted our time?
No...
I think it's beautiful.
Right... Yes.
It's beautiful.
The universe is so big.
Yeah.
The stars look so yummy,
like sugar spread all over.
What the heck?
Lord Damian laughed.
Whatever, shut up.
Hey, we're gonna start heading back.
Oh, yeah. This was supposed
to be a field research trip.
Make sure you three write reports.
Ugh... Once we get back, I just
want to shower and go right to bed.
That sounds very healthy, lad.
Master Henderson...
I've brought the boys'
field research reports.
Thank you, Mr. Green.
Were they able to spread their wings?
I hope they felt that way.
Quite elegant.
We saw a lot and did a
bunch of stuff. It was fun.
But we'll have to work on his spelling.
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
MISSION AND FAMILY
THE ELEGANT BONDMAN
THE HEART OF A CHILD/WAKING UP